Guide to the Seven Woods Press Records 1970-1986
University of Chicago Library
Seven Woods Press. Records
1970-1986
16.5 linear feet (28 boxes)
Hanna Holborn Gray Special Collections Research Center University of Chicago Library 1100 East 57th Street Chicago, Illinois 60637 U.S.A.
The Seven Woods Press was founded by George Koppelman in 1972. The Seven Woods Press Records document aspects of the publisher from beginning to end of operation, including financial, production and distribution records, advertising and promotional material, correspondence, manuscripts, reviews, magazines, newspapers, and photographs. It also includes material from other poetry and publication businesses.
Information on Use
Access
Series IV, Restricted, includes financial material that is restricted until 2033.
The remainder of the collection is open for research.
Historical Note
Seven Woods Press, founded by George Koppelman, was a small, New York based publishing company that operated from 1972-1981. The press concentrated on poetry books, producing seven collections of poetry as well as several broadsides and chapbooks. Some of the authors published by Seven Woods Press include University of Chicago alumnus Susan Fromberg Schaeffer, Chicago native Albert Goldbarth, Jay Wright, winner of MacArthur “genius” award, and Frances Mayes.
George Koppelman graduated from the University of Chicago (S.B. 1961) and operated Seven Woods Press from 1972-1981. Following this, Koppelman was a programmer for IBM. Upon retiring from programming, Koppelman began “Cultured Oyster Books,” a mail-order rare book business specializing in contemporary literature. In 1995 Koppelman became a member of the Grolier Club.
Scope Note
The Seven Woods Press Records are divided into four series: Series I, Administrative; Series II, Publications; Series III, Oversize; Series IV, Restricted. The Seven Woods Press Records document aspects of the publisher from beginning to end of operation, including financial, production and distribution records, advertising and promotional material, correspondence, manuscripts, reviews, magazines, newspapers, and photographs. It also includes material from other poetry and publication businesses.
Series I, Administrative, contains financial and production records, advertisements and publicity, articles, reviews, ephemera, photographs, and correspondence. The financial and production records are primarily invoices, receipts, and book orders, as well as production materials about type setting, printing and design, and other publishing services used. The advertising material is correspondence with publications such as The New York Times and Harpers, as well as fliers, magazines and posters with advertisements. The correspondence is primarily from authors and poets, as well as other business and personal correspondence with George Koppelman. There are also applications for awards and grants. Other material pertains to the publishing industry in general, including materials from other press companies, events and exhibits, and correspondence from various organizations. Reviews and articles are in publications such as Publisher’s Weekly, Time, Margins, Library Journal and Small Press Review. See Series II for additional correspondence. See Series III for additional administrative material.
Series II, Publications, contains manuscripts, proofs, correspondence, publicity and reviews for the publications produced by Seven Woods Press. Most correspondence is between Koppelman and the authors, and some is concerned with research and production. Also included are designs and artwork for the publication covers and title pages, and proofs from the design and printing company Profile Press. There is also information about and manuscripts from individual authors. See Series I for additional correspondence. See Series III for additional publication materials.
Series III, Oversize, contains magazines, newspapers, reviews, proofs, articles, and publicity. There are posters and ephemera advertising events and conferences as well as for poetry readings from The Academy of American Poets, The Manhattan Theatre Club, and The Poetry Center. See Series I for additional administrative material. See Series II for additional publications material.
Series IV, Restricted, includes financial material that is restricted until 2033.
Related Resources
Browse finding aids by topic.
Subject Headings
Balazs, Mary; Cohen, Marion Deutsche, 1943-; Doreski, William; Goldbarth, Albert; Koppelman, George; Mayes, Frances; Molesworth, Charles, 1941-; Ruth, Barbara; Schaeffer, Susan Fromberg; Sher, Steven; Waldrop, Rosmarie; Whiting, Nathan, 1946-; Wright, Jay, 1934-; Seven Woods Press; American poetry -- 20th century; Poetry; Small Presses
INVENTORY
- Series I: Administrative
  - Advertising, 1972-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advertising, 1972-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Advertising, 1972-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Advertising, 1972-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Bookseller Association, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Council for the Arts, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Library Association, 1972-1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Library Association, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Library Association, 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Articles, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Articles, 1973-1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Association of American Publishers, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Awards and Prizes, 1976-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Awards and Prizes, 1976-1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Book Affair, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Book Exhibits, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Book Exhibits, 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Book Exhibits, The Combined Book Exhibit, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Book Exhibits, New York Book Fair, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Book Exhibits, New York Book Fair, 1974-1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Book Exhibits, New York Book Fair, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Book Sellers, Quarto Book Service, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Broadsides, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Brochures, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Charitable Contributions, 1972-1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Conferences, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Coordinating Council of Literary Magazines, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Advance Book Information, 1972-1981 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Chapbooks, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Chapbooks, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Complaints, 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Early Production, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, General, 1971-1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, General, 1972-1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, General, 1972-1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Inquiries for Publication, 1970-1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Inquiries for Publication, 1970-1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Inquiries for Publication, 1970-1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Inquiries for Publication, 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Inquiries for Publication, 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Inquiries for Publication, 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Inquiries for Publication, 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Inquiries for Publication, 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Inquiries for Publication, 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Inquiries for Publication, 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Inquiries for Publication, 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Inquiries for Publication, 1970-1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Inquiries for Publication, 1970-1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Legal, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Questionnaires, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Requests for Catalogs, 1973-1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Requests for Catalogs, 1973-1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Dustbooks, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Events, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Koppelman, George, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Literary Agents, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Library of Congress, 1973-1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Mini Storage, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1974-1980 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, Application Guidelines, 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, Program Guides 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, 1974-1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, "Manhattan Book Hound," 1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, "Meridian," 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters, "Poetry Flash," 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters, "Two Hands News," 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - New York Small Press Association, 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - New York Small Press Association, 1977-1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Orders, Accounts Paid, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Orders, Accounts Payable, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Orders, Accounts Receivable, 1979-1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Orders, Bookstores, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Orders, Delinquent Accounts, 1976-1980 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Orders, Expense Receipts, 1971-1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Orders, First Orders, 1975-1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Orders, Fulfillment, 1973-1981 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Orders, Fulfillment, 1973-1981 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Other Press Companies, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Other Press Companies, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Other Press Companies, 1974-1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Other Press Companies, 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - The Poetry Center, 1973-1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Poetry Readings, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Poets and Writers, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Postal Affairs, 1972-1981 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Profile Press, 1976-1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Publisher's Weekly, 1972-1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Publisher's Weekly, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Publishing Services, 1975-1982 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Publishing Services, 1975-1986 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Publishing Services, 1978-1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Requests for Updated Book List, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Returns, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Reviews, 1972-1978 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Small Press Review, 1974-1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Small Press Review, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Tape Cassette Duplication Service, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Type Setting, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Wholesale, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Series II: Publications
  - Balazs, Mary, The Stones Refuse Their Peace, Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Balazs, Mary, The Stones Refuse Their Peace, Correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Balazs, Mary, The Stones Refuse Their Peace, Manuscript, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Balazs, Mary, The Stones Refuse Their Peace, Manuscript, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Balazs, Mary, The Stones Refuse Their Peace, Manuscript, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Balazs, Mary, The Stones Refuse Their Peace, Manuscript, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Balazs, Mary, The Stones Refuse Their Peace, Manuscript, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Balazs, Mary, The Stones Refuse Their Peace, Proof, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Balazs, Mary, The Stones Refuse Their Peace, Proof, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Balazs, Mary, The Stones Refuse Their Peace, Reviews, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Cohen, Marion, The Weirdest is the Sphere, Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Cohen, Marion, The Weirdest is the Sphere, Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cohen, Marion, The Weirdest is the Sphere, Manuscript, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Cohen, Marion, The Weirdest is the Sphere, Manuscript, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Cohen, Marion, The Weirdest is the Sphere, Manuscript, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Cohen, Marion, The Weirdest is the Sphere, Proof, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Cohen, Marion, Manuscript, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Artwork, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Colophon sheets, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Correspondence, 1975-1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Cover, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Manuscript, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Profile Press, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Proof, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Proof, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Proof, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Proof, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Proof, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Proof, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Proof, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Proof, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Research, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Reviews, 1976-1981 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Doreski, William, The Old Age of the Opera, Manuscript, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Card Catalog Request, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Colophon Sheets, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Correspondence, 1974-1982 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Cover, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, ISBN, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Manuscript, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Manuscript, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Manuscript, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Manuscript, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Manuscript, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Profile Press, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Proof, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Proof, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Proof, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Proof, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Proof, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Proof, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Proof, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Proof, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Proof, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Proof, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Proof, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Proof, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Publicity, 1974-1976 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Reviews, 1974-1979 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Away, Manuscript, 1978-1981 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Manusrcript, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Cover, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Manuscript, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Manuscript, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Manuscript, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Manuscript, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Production, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Proof, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Proof, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Proof, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Proof, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Proof, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Publicity, 1978-1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Reviews, 1978-1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Mayes, Frances, Climbing Aconcagua, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Cover, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Manuscript, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Manuscript, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Manuscript, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Production, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Proof, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Proof, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Proof, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Proof, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Proof, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Proof, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Proof, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Reviews, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Oles, Carol, Coming into the United Society of Believers, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Oles, Carol, Coming into the United Society of Believers, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Ruth, Barbara, The Politics of Relationships, Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Ruth, Barbara, The Politics of Relationships, Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Ruth, Barbara, The Politics of Relationships, Proof, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Ruth, Barbara, The Politics of Relationships, Proof, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Ruth, Barbara, The Politics of Relationships, Proof, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Ruth, Barbara, The Politics of Relationships, Proof, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Ruth, Barbara, The Politics of Relationships, Proof, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Ruth, Barbara, The Politics of Relationships, Proof, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Ruth, Barbara, The Politics of Relationships, Proof, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Ruth, Barbara, The Politics of Relationships, Proof, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Ruth, Barbara, Manuscript, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Card Catalog Request, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Copyright, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Correspondence, 1970-1981 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Cover, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Cover, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Manuscript, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Manuscript, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Manuscript, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Manuscript, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Manuscript, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Manuscript, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Profile Press, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Proof, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Proof, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Proof, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Reviews, 1972-1979 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Reviews, 1972-1979 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Sher, Steven, Persnickety, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Sher, Steven, Persnickety, 1978-1982 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Waldrop, Rosmarie, The Ambition of Ghosts, Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Waldrop, Rosmarie, The Ambition of Ghosts, Manuscript, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Waldrop, Rosmarie, The Ambition of Ghosts, Proof, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Transitions, Card Catalog Request, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Transitions, Copyright, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Transitions, Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Transitions, Cover Art, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Transitions, Manuscript, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Transitions, Manuscript, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Transitions, Manuscript, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Transitions, Proof, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Transitions, Proof, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Transitions, Proof, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Transitions, Proof, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Transitions, Publicity, 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Transitions, Reviews, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Transitions, Reviews, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Manuscript, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Whiting, Nathan, Personal, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Correspondence, 1977-1982 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Cover, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Manuscript, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Manuscript, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Manuscript, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Profile Press, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Proof, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Proof, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Proof, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Proof, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Reviews, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Series III: Oversize
  - Broadsides, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Brochures, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 2)